Privacy Policy - Washington State Local Health Insurance - CHPW                                                               

Search  

MENUMENU

[Home](https://www.chpw.org/) › Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

##### 

Our site does not share or release your personal information.

* ### EXPLORE MORE!

* 
    
    #### Explore your care and your community.
    
    Follow our blog for the latest in health and wellness from CHPW and local health leaders.

Web Privacy Statement and Policy
--------------------------------

When you browse our website, the site gathers no personally identifiable information about you. Examples of your personally identifiable information include your name, Social Security number, address, telephone number, race/ethnicity, language, account number, employment, medical history, health records, claims information, etc.

If you complete and submit an online information request form, we capture only the information that you supply and only use it to fulfill your request. Participation in online surveys is voluntary and will not impact your health care coverage or benefits. CHPW may use your responses to improve services and/or for marketing purposes.

With few exceptions, we do not share personal information you enter on a form or on our website that might identify you, such as your full name, street address, telephone number, or email address with third parties.

### Exceptions

We might release personally identifiable information you submit to us on this site in these cases:

* We do sometimes share information that you enter with our trusted business partners, who have agreed to follow our privacy policies.
* We will release specific information about you to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.
* We may also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of our website, or a threat of harm to you or others.
* We may also use information you give us to help improve our site’s usability.

To learn more about how CHPW protects personally identifiable information, please [download our Notice of Privacy Practices.](https://www.chpw.org/wp-content/uploads/content/member-center/Medicaid_Notice_of_Privacy_Practice.pdf "Click to open the pdf document of our Notice of Privacy Practice.")

### Non-personally identifiable information and the use of cookie technology

We collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of “cookie” technology and/or IP address tracking. Non-personally identifiable information might include the browser you use, the type of computer, smartphone, or other device you are using, your operating system, your Internet service provider, and other similar information. Your member ID number or profile information is not stored in cookies.

We use such information in the aggregate to understand how our users, as a group, use the services and resources provided on our site. When we say we use the information in the aggregate, that means that information from a group of individuals has been compiled and processed so that no one individual’s information can be isolated. We study aggregate information to learn which areas of [chpw.org](https://www.chpw.org/) are most popular, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may improve [chpw.org](https://www.chpw.org/).

Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some features of [chpw.org](https://www.chpw.org/) may not function properly.

DID YOU KNOW...?
----------------

\[random\_content group\_id='25' num\_posts='1'\]

* 
* CUSTOMER SERVICE
* [\[email protected\]](https://www.chpw.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* 
* NURSE ADVICE LINE
* (CHPW Members)

* 
* CASE MANAGEMENT  
    TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE
* (CHPW Members)

* 
* ADDRESS

* 
* HOURS
* 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.
* Monday through Friday

* 
* ADDRESS

#### QUICK LINKS

* MEMBERS

* PLANS

* PROVIDERS

* OTHER

* 

Last Update Date: August 27, 2024

Community Health Plan of Washington (CHPW) was founded in 1992 by Washington’s community health centers. CHPW is committed to Washington's health. To enroll in a Community Health Plan of Washington [Apple Health (Medicaid)](https://www.chpw.org/find-health-plan/apple-health-plan/our-regions/), [Medicare Advantage](https://medicare.chpw.org/contact-us/chpw-representatives/), or [Individual & Family Cascade Select](https://individualandfamily.chpw.org/individual-and-family-plans/cascade-select-plan-finder/) plans, you must be eligible and live in the service areas. This is not a complete description of benefit. Please contact us for more information.

##### Language Assistance

Language assistance services, including interpreters and translation of printed materials, are available free of charge.

[Español | 中文 | Tiếng Việt | 한국어 | Tagalog | Pусский | العربية | Kreyòl | Français | Polski | Português | Italiano | Deutsch | 日本語 | فارسی | Other Languages…](https://www.chpw.org/contact-us/language-assistance/ "Language Assistance Services")

You will need Adobe reader to open PDFs on the site. [Download the free version on Adobe Reader.](https://get.adobe.com/reader/otherversions/ "Download Acrobat Reader - Free Version")

Copyright ©2024 Community Health Plan of Washington

☏ HAVE QUESTIONS ?
------------------

#### Get real answers  
from real people

Phone: [1-800-440-1561](tel:11-800-440-1561 "Contact us today and get help.")  
[\[email protected\]](https://www.chpw.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

x

[The owner of this website has made a commitment to accessibility and inclusion, please report any problems that you encounter using the contact form on this website. This site uses the WP ADA Compliance Check plugin to enhance accessibility.](https://www.wpadacompliance.com/ "Click this link to learn more about the WP ADA Compliance plugin.") ‪
